Guide to the Lynne Tillman Papers 1939-2008 (Bulk 1984-2006) MSS 180 MSS 180
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Series I, Subseries B: Incomplete Names / Illegible / Unsigned / Other Correspondence
    - Jema, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 181)
    - Jessica, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 182)
    - Jesus, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 183)
    - Jim, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 184)
    - Jim and Rachel, Undated (Box 7, Folder 185)
    - Jim and Ruth, Undated (Box 7, Folder 186)
    - Jo, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Joan, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Joanna, Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Joe / The Media Show, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Joel, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - John, 1982-1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - John D., 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - John O., 1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Jonathan, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Joy and Darius, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Judy, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Justin, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - K., Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Karen, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Karyn, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Kasia, c.a. 1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Kate, c.a. 1972 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Katherine, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Kendall, 1993-2002 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Kerry, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Kit, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - L., 1975-1993 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Larry, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Laura, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Laura and David, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Leander, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Leonard and Dorothy, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Letia, Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Levi, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Lidia and Devin, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Lin and Dave, Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Linda, 1993-2002 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Linette, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Lisa, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Louise, [1974] (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Lucas, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Lucy, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Lydia, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Lydia, Alan, Theo and Daniel, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Lynn, 1983-1994 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - M., 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Mandy, c.a. 1991 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Margo, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Maria, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Mario, [1994] (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Mark and Bea, [2004] (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Marsha, 1998-2002 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Martha, 1976-1998 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Mary, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Mathew, Undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Matt, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Matthew, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Maya, Undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Meena, Undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Mel, Undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Michael, 1970-1989 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Mike, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Millicent, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Mimi, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Mina, Undated (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Ming-Wei, Undated (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Mitch, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - [Moritos], 1989 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - N., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Nancy, Undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Naomi, Undated (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Narie, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - [Nashina], 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Nektaria, c.a. 1992 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Nic, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Nicholas, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Pat, Undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Paul H., 1992 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Peggy, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Pete, Undated (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Peter, Undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Peter, Chloe, Kaye and Viggo, [1994-2000] (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - P.J. and H.B., 1983-1998 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Philip, c.a. 1998 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Pietro, Undated (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Power, 197[6] (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - R., c.a. 2002 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Raissa, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Ralph, 1973-1980 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Rebecca / Sight and Sound, Undated (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Rene, c.a. 1988 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Reno, Undated (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Riley, Undated (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Roanna, Undated (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Robert, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Rodney, c.a. 1995 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Roger, c.a. 2003 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Rosi, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Rosie, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Rudy, 19[8]4 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - S., 1989-2005 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Sally, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Sara [Roszak], Undated (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Sarah, 1991-1997 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Scarlett, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Scott, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - [Serge], Undated (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Sheila, 1980-1994 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Simon, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Smitty, Undated (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Somini, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Steve, 1988-1997 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Steven, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Susan, 1985-1999 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Susanna, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Suzanne, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Tam, 1993-1997 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Ted, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Thyan, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Tim, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Tim and Johanne, Undated (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Thomas, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Todd, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Tom, 1977-1992 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Tom and Deborah, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - [Vance], 1983-1997 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Vik and Janaina, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Vivian, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Willy, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Yan, c.a. 1996 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Yo, Undated (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Unknown Sender, 1972-1999 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Unsigned / Illegible, 1972-2003 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Unsigned / Illegible - Typed concrete poetry, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Inserts separated from correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - E-mail print-outs, Bulk 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence originally housed with audio tapes 180.0128 and 180.0201, 04/06/1995 (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Series I, Subseries C: Sent by Lynne Tillman
    - Aminoff, Judith (Gintz-), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Beyond Baroque Board Members, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Brooks, Mel, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Chomont, Tom, Undated (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Clark[e], Lisa, c.a. 1995 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Cohen, Ira, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Cohen, Randy, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Coxhead, Susan and David, Undated (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - District Attorney of the County of New York, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Dorsky, Nick, Undated (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Dugger, John and David Medalla, Undated (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Engelman, Peter, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Ford, Charles Henri, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - Fuchs, Miriam; Robert Siegle, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - Gianelli, Ida, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - Görtler, Dirk, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - Hakasuisha Publishers, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - Hofstra, David, 1980-1992 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - Jones, Christopher, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 151)
    - Joris, Pierre, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 152)
    - Kaplan, Helen, Undated (Box 8, Folder 153)
    - Kim, John; "Neil and Simon", 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - Lawson, Emma, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - LeGrice, Malcolm, Undated (Box 8, Folder 156)
    - Levy, Bill, Undated (Box 8, Folder 157)
    - MacCabe, Colin, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - Mannheim, Peter, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 159)
    - Martin, Sarah, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 160)
    - Michell, John, Undated (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Murphy, Jay, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 162)
    - [Oakley], Lucy and Marvin, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - O'Grady, Elisa, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - Random House, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 165)
    - Rommell, Wanda, Undated (Box 8, Folder 166)
    - Sheedy, Charlotte, c.a. 1987 (Box 8, Folder 167)
    - Simon & Schuster / Nita Krygier-Fox, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 168)
    - Stromfeld/Roter Stern / Janis Osolin, 1984-1995 (Box 8, Folder 169)
    - Terlevic, Franca, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 170)
    - Tiz, Colle, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 171)
    - Trokenheim, Matthew, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 172)
    - Withers, Josephine, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 173)
    - Incomplete / Unknown recipient / Other, Bulk 1996-2004 (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - Series I, Subseries D: Correspondence Files (Box 7, Folder 64)
    Scope and Content note
    Series I, Subseries D contains material pertaining to Lynne Tillman's correspondents on whom she extensively researched, or whose correspondence contains significant amounts of creative work.
    - Beiles, Sinclair: Note removed from "Ballets?" by Beiles and Jemima Hunt, Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Beiles, Sinclair: Plays - "The Personel Officer," "The Gay Young Things" and "The Pact", c.a. 1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Beiles, Sinclair: Poetry; press; correspondence, 1980, c.a. 1991 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Bowles, Paul: Correspondence; articles/obituaries, 1973-1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Bowles, Paul: Prints of Bowle, Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
      General
      Credit: Lynne Tillman
    - Bowles, Paul: Prints of Bowle, Tillman and Buffie Johnson in Tangier, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Credit: David Hostra
    - Bowles, Paul: Prints of Bowle at an Atlanta, Georgia party, c.a. 1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Ford, Charles Henri: Correspondence; articles/obituaries; creative work; etc., 1969-2003 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Oversize
      Two pieces in an oversize folder
    - Ford, Charles Henri: "Selected Poems by Charles Henri Ford from his book 'Flag of Ecstasy' (Black Sparrow Press, 1972)", c.a. 1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Ford, Charles Henri: Slides and color print-outs of Ford and Tillman, Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Mathews, Harry, (1973-2001?) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Oppenheim, Meret: Drafts of "Don't Cry.... Work" (Tillman and Carla Liss interview of Oppenheim); correspondence; transcripts/field notes; IMAGO Meret Oppenheim film program, 1973-1996 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Oppenheim, Meret: Prints, contact sheets and negatives, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Rattray, David G.: Correspondence; articles; poetry; artwork, 1961-1992 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Rattray: David G.: Translation of Antonin Artaud letters for SULFUR #9, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Series II: Subject Files
  Series II: Subject Files, contains material pertaining to Tillman's work and research as a critic and writer, and is also indicative of her participation in a larger artistic community. These include original creative work, drafts, and research produced by Tillman and other artists, as well as announcements of performances and events, and other related articles.
  The material is arranged alphabetically by artist(s), venue/organizer or subject where possible. Events/works with numerous participating artists are listed by title. This series is separated into three subseries:
  A: Artists
  B: Subjects
  C: Photographic Materials and Miscellaneous
  - Series II, Subseries A: Artists
    - Abraham, Ralph, c.a. 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Acker, Kathy, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Adweek, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Agar, Eileen, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Ahwesh, Peggy, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Albery, Nicholas, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Allyn, Jerri, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - American Center, c.a. 1994 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Ames, Jonathan, Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Andrews, George, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Angus, James ***see also*** Oversize Series II, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Anthony, William, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Armstrong, David***see also***Oversize Series II, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Arnoldi, Katherine, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Arrizabalaga, Leonardo, Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - The Art Party, Undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Artists Space, 1981-1987 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - The Auros Group for New Music, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - B, Beth, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Back Room: A Video Program curated for The Abortion Project, Part II, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Band of George, Undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Baracz, Jan, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Barnes and Noble, c.a. 1997 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Barry, Judith, 1985-1995 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Bartle, R.A., Bill Bell and Noa Hall, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Bartlett, Neil, Undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Barton, Nancy, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Baskerville+Watson, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      Postcard event announcement. Participants include Nan Goldin.
    - Bassara, Robert, 1997-2004 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Bee, Susan, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Bell, Hilary, c.a. 1996 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Bellamy, Dodie and Kevin Killian, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Bellmer, Hans, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Bergreen, Karen, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - The Bettys, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Blachly, Jimbo, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Blagg, Max, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Blair, Dick and Jerry Phillips, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Bloom, Barbara, 1991-1999 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Blum, Andrea, c.a. 1997 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Bockris, Victor, [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - BOMB Magazine, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Bordowitz, Gregg, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Bornstein, Jennifer, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Bourgeois, Louise, 1996-2003 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Breuer, Marco, 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Brown, Marie-Annick, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Brown, Wesley, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Buckley, Carmel, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Burckhardt, Rudy, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Burstein, Jessica, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Caire, Patrice, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Campo Baeza, Alberto, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Capa, Hubert (pseudonym), 1993 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Carey, Ellen, 1998-2002 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Carnegie Hall, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 71)
      Stagebill for Tibetan New Year's Celebration performance featuring David Bowie, Dana Bryant, Philip Glass, and more.
    - The Century Association, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - The Charles Cowles Gallery, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Charles, Denis, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Chase, Edward T., 1964-1997 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Clair, Stephen (Steve Ferguson), 1996 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Clark, Emilie, c.a. 2002 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Clark, Michael, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Clarke, Cheryl, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Clementine Gallery, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Cockcroft, Eva, Undated (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Cohen, Ze'eva, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Colo, Papo, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Colomina, Beatriz, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Cooper, Dennis, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Corner, Philip, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Cortez, Diego, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Cox, Renée, Undated (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Crary, Jonathan, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Curt Marcus Gallery, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Cyphers, Peggy, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Darboven, Hanne, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Davis, Lydia, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Davis, Taylor, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Davis, Tim and John Godfrey, Undated (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - DeCarava, Ray, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - de Filippi, Fernando, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - de Saint Phalle, Niki, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Deutsch, David, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Diao, David, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Dickson, Jane, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Dillon, Millicent, c.a. 2000 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Dion, Mark, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Debord, Guy, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - DNA Gallery, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - The Drawing Center, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Dreher, Peter, 1996-2002 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Drozdik, Orshi, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Dullsville, Undated (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Durant, Mark Alice, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Ebersole, Lucinda, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Einzig, Melanie, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Ellis, Stephen, 1986-1994 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Emigholz, Heinz, 1985-2000 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Engler, Brigitte, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Eno, Brian, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Epstein, Mitch, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Erhardt, Jean, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Ess, Barbara, 1979-2001 (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Exit Art ***see also*** Oversize Series II, Subseries A, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Fagin, Steve, 199[8] (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Fairchild, B. H., 2002 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Fales Library, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Falour, Lisa B., 2000 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Fence, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Films de Femmes, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Findeisen, Raoul David, c.a. 1997 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Firestone, Shulamith, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Flynt, Robert, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Ford, Charles Henri, 1979-2003 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Ford, Charles Henri: Manuscript of "Life of a Child," part 1, Undated (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Ford, Charles Henri: Manuscript of "Life of a Child," part 2, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Fordham University, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Symposium on the legacy of Marshall McLuhan
    - Foster, Ken, 1998-2002 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - The Foundry Theatre, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Frailey, Stephen, Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Francis, Linda, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Franklin Furnace, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Fraser, Andrea, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Fuller, Margaret / David Salle, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Gaddis, William, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Gallagher, Ellen, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Gardner, Donald, Undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Garnet, Eldon, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Garrard, Rose, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Genzken, Isa, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Gerbault, Arthur, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Gerson, Neville, Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - "Get High Off the Midgets in El Salvador", Undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Gill, Brendan, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Ginka + Takako, 199[?] (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Ginsberg, Martha, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Giorno, John, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Glier, Mike, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Glück, Robert, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Gordimer, Nadine, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Görtler, Dirk / Chelsea Hotel Magazine, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Gourevitch, Philip, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Greenwald, Ted, c.a. 1980 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Grey Room, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Gross, Larry: Manuscript of "You Don't Know Where This Starts or Ends", Undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Guston, Philip, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Hailand, Tim, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Halley, Peter and Frank Kozik; Organized by Bob Nickas, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Hankowitz, Molly, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Harris, Lyle Ashton, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Harrison, Julie, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Hartley, Pat, Undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Hatje, Hannes, 1986-1991 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Hayman, Richard, Undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Hearn, Pat, 1995-2001 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      Two pieces moved to oversize folder
    - Heartfield, John, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Hegge, James, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Heilmann, Mary, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Hein, Birgit, c.a. 1995 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Hell, Richard, c.a. 2001 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Hill, Rebecca, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Hiller, Susan, 1983-2001 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Hodges, Jim, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Hofstra, David: Agreements; correspondence; misc., c.a. 1990-1997 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers; press clippings; press release; notes; lyrics (with Tillman); misc., c.a. 1975-1980 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers; invoices, c.a. 1981 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      Handwritten performance notes/cheat sheets present on reverse side of some posters.
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers; press clippings; photographs, c.a. 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Hofstra, David: Portraits by Andrew Hill and unknown photographer(s), c.a. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers; press clippings; touring information; misc., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers; press clippings; notes, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance programmes; press clippings; press release, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers and programmes; press clippings; misc., 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Hofstra, David: Performance announcement fliers and programmes; press clippings; misc., 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Hofstra, David: Curriculum vitae / Discography, Undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Hofstra, Leonard, c.a. 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Holch, Meredith, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Holland, Robin, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Holzer, Jenny, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Home, Stewart: Articles and drafts of collaborations with Tillman; miscellaneous artwork, c.a. 2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Home, Stewart: Manuscript of "Cunt", Undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Home, Stewart: Manuscript of "69 Things to Do with a Dead Princess", Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Home, Stewart: News clippings, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Horn, Roni, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Housing Works, c.a. 2005 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Howard, Richard, Undated (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Howland, Rebecca, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Hujar, Peter, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Hull, Steven, 1998-2002 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Hunter College, 1984-1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Indiana, Gary, c.a. 1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - International Center of Photography, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Jackson, Shelley, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Jaffe, Shirley, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Jarman, Derek, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Jellett, Mainie, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Jenkins, Janet, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Jerriese Johnson East Village Gospel Choir, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Johnston, Jill, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Jones, Bill T. and Arnie Zane, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Jones, Finola, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Jüdisches Museum der Stadt Wien, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Julien, Isaac, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Jusidman, Yishai, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Just Another Asshole, c.a. 1983 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Just, Marcel, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Kaplan, Daile, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Kaplan, Helene, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Kasper, M., 1985 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Katz, Leandro, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Keller, Marjorie, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Kelly, Mary, 1974-1990 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Kennedy, William, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Kettell Musial, Linda, Undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Khedoori, Toba, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Kiernan, Frances, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Kiesler, Lillian, 1979-2002 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Killing Joke, Undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - The Kitchen, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Knowlton, Win, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Kohlhofer, Christof, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Kolbowski, Silvia ***see also*** Oversize Series II, Subseries A, 1995-2004 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Kooning, Willem de, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Kramer, Margia, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 1984-2001 (Box 11, Folder 47)